You completed our lesson on cleaning data,
أكملنا درس تنظيف البيانات،
the third step in the data wrangling process.
الخطوة الثالثة في عملية معالجة البيانات.
That also means you've reached the end of our data wrangling course.
وهذا يعني أيضًا أنكم وصلتم إلى نهاية دورة معالجة البيانات.
Congratulations. In this lesson,
تهانينا. في هذا الدرس،
you converted your assessments from the previous lesson and defined,
لقد قمت بتحويل التقييمات من الدرس السابق وعمليات التنظيف المحددة
coded, and tested cleaning operations for them.
والمشفرة والتي تم اختبارها لهذه التقييمات.
You cleaned to improve quality and you did it efficiently using things like loops,
لقد قمت بالتنظيف لتحسين الجودة وقمت بذلك بكفاءة عالية باستخدام أشياء مثل loops
functions, and regular expressions.
والدالات والتعبيرات العادية.
You also cleaned to tidy the data set using pandas's tidying functions, like melt.
كما قمت بالتنظيف لترتيب مجموعة البيانات باستخدام الدالات المرتبة في pandas، مثل melt.
That was a lot of cleaning and the code required wasn't a piece of cake.
حيث إن الكثير من التنظيف والتعليمات البرمجية المطلوبة لم تكن قطعة من الكعكة.
You should be proud of yourself and excited,
يجب أن تكون فخورًا بنفسك ومتحمسًا،
because everything you cleaned represents
لأن كل ما قمت بتنظيفه يمثل
the vast majority of issues you'll encounter in the future.
الغالبية العظمى من المشاكل التي ستواجهها في المستقبل.
And congrats on completing the course once again.
وتهانينا على إكمال الدورة التدريبية مرة أخرى.
You're a certified data gatherer, assessor and cleaner.
أنت تمثل جامع البيانات المعتمد والقائم على عملية التقييم والنظافة.
Since so much of the world's data comes
نظرًا لأن الكثير من البيانات حول العالم تأتي
dirty and messy and so much new data is being produced every day,
مهملة وفوضوية ويتم إنتاج الكثير من البيانات الجديدة كل يوم،
you'll have plenty of opportunities to apply your new wrangling skills.
سيكون لديك الكثير من الفرص لتطبيق مهارات المعالجة الجديدة.